Revisit the dark side of desire.
Secret Games 3 is a thriller, drama film directed by Gregory Dark.
A neglected housewife of a busy husband who is a doctor
turns to prostitution to pass the time.
One of her customers develops an obsession with her and begins stalking her.
Terrell, played by Woody Brown.
Diana Larson, played by Rochelle Swanson.
Alex Larson, played by Dean Scofield.
Ruthie, played by Brenda Swanson.
Gwen, played by May Karasun.
Louis, played by Bob Delegall.
Secret Games 3 is a 1994 American erotic thriller drama film
directed by Gregory Dark and produced by Andrew W.
This film has music composed by Ashley Irwin, and starred Woody Brown,
Rochelle Swanson, May Karasun and Dean Scofield in the lead roles.
This (currently) is the third and final film in the Secret Games film trilogy.
The tone is emotional and intense.